hollywire.com 2011-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Hollywire.com

**Hollywire.com** is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. **Hollywire** will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by **Hollywire.com**. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, **Hollywire** may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information. 

We share non-personal information about your activity at our Web site with **Six Apart LTD**. and its authorized partners for the purpose of tailoring, analyzing, and reporting on advertising you see. **Six Apart Ltd**. may use or authorize the use of cookies, pixels, Web beacons and/or other technologies to tailor the ads you see here and at other Web sites you may visit. For more information, please see **Six Apart Ltd,'s** privacy policy at <http://www.sixapart.com/privacy>. 

To get in touch with **Hollywire** , please email us at: [info@hollywire.com](mailto:info@hollywire.com)

  * You played it to the beat!
  * So many good times tonight w/ @Yay_its_Jennie @Chelsea_Briggs @lindsayzir + @sarascoggins! Feeling thankful + happy for such fab people :)
  * Thx wayne! Excited! Let's do it! RT @WayneLAdams: Happy Birthday @Chelsea_Briggs I love & miss ya as always Chel! I'll be in LA in Sep! !
  * Adding our final touches whilst in @Chelsea_Briggs apt! #Dorks http://lockerz.com/s/101413689
  * http://lockerz.com/s/101407222 Flowers at my door from @Jneill10 !! Wow, I sure feel like I'm getting spoiled (cont) http://tl.gd/aemsk9
  * So very excited for SOHO House tonight w/my fav ladies for @yay_its_jennie 's Grad celebration! @lindsayzir @Katie_Krause & @sarascoggins :)
  * @crystalfambrini thanks so much Crystal! You are the sweetest ever!! Thanks for always being so supportive and positive! Xo
  * Thanks!!! Xo :) RT @JoslynDavis: @Chelsea_Briggs girl!!! Happpppppy Birthday to you!!!! Oxoxox
  * Getting all snazzed up for @Yay_its_Jennie's graduation dinner at SoHo house! #CelebrationTime
